[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "When you look back on this career you've had?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "this", "career", "you", "'ve", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "I mean I've had people come up to me in airports.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "'ve", "had", "people", "come", "up", "to", "me", "in", "airports", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you miss the daily connection?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "miss", "the", "daily", "connection", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I don't miss the daily of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "miss", "the", "daily", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Really, so you didn't repeat very often?", "question_tokens": ["Really", ",", "so", "you", "did", "n't", "repeat", "very", "often", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do you think of the way that television has evolved since your daily show stopped?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "way", "that", "television", "has", "evolved", "since", "your", "daily", "show", "stopped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "ONAHUE: Well, you know, it's hard for me to -- I don't want to criticize them, because I took a lot of heat.", "answer_tokens": ["ONAHUE", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "me", "to", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "criticize", "them", ",", "because", "I", "took", "a", "lot", "of", "heat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "It would be strange if you did approve of it all in a sense, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "strange", "if", "you", "did", "approve", "of", "it", "all", "in", "a", "sense", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Yes, and we were always -- I mean we were always different.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "we", "were", "always", "--", "I", "mean", "we", "were", "always", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "And what was the reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "the", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Oh, well, everybody thought that their kids would catch it if they watched it.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "everybody", "thought", "that", "their", "kids", "would", "catch", "it", "if", "they", "watched", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mohamed Ali"]}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "If I could let you do one again tomorrow, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "let", "you", "do", "one", "again", "tomorrow", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "We had a very good program with Mohamed Ali.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "very", "good", "program", "with", "Mohamed", "Ali", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlo"]}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 138, "question": "You know, he was one of the great boxers in history, but he also had this phenomenal brain and humor and self-marketing style which you just -- you don't get that package, do you, very often?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "he", "was", "one", "of", "the", "great", "boxers", "in", "history", ",", "but", "he", "also", "had", "this", "phenomenal", "brain", "and", "humor", "and", "self-marketing", "style", "which", "you", "just", "--", "you", "do", "n't", "get", "that", "package", ",", "do", "you", ",", "very", "often", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Marlo did a book titled \"The Right Words at the Right Time.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Marlo", "did", "a", "book", "titled", "``", "The", "Right", "Words", "at", "the", "Right", "Time", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Completely.", "answer_tokens": ["Completely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What do you make of the Rick Santorum surge?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "Rick", "Santorum", "surge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "One of many.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "And I'm like, here's a guy who basically repeatedly says I support the constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "'m", "like", ",", "here", "'s", "a", "guy", "who", "basically", "repeatedly", "says", "I", "support", "the", "constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "A president says when I get into power, I'm going to make it more available for poor people to have better health care than they're getting already and this is an abject miserable failure that he should be lambasted for?", "question_tokens": ["A", "president", "says", "when", "I", "get", "into", "power", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "make", "it", "more", "available", "for", "poor", "people", "to", "have", "better", "health", "care", "than", "they", "'re", "getting", "already", "and", "this", "is", "an", "abject", "miserable", "failure", "that", "he", "should", "be", "lambasted", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "He's calling for a nanny government.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "calling", "for", "a", "nanny", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "When you look back, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Well, it is certainly true that -- first of all, I was a single parent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "certainly", "true", "that", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "was", "a", "single", "parent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "What do you think of Oprah?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Oprah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I think Oprah has risen to a level in the stratosphere unknown to all of us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Oprah", "has", "risen", "to", "a", "level", "in", "the", "stratosphere", "unknown", "to", "all", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Why, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Well, I think she's -- she's a compelling personality.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "she", "'s", "--", "she", "'s", "a", "compelling", "personality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Look at my own early history.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "at", "my", "own", "early", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "That's a pretty good endorsement, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "pretty", "good", "endorsement", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Try a bit of -- a bit of not dealing with just the friendly fire all the time?", "question_tokens": ["Try", "a", "bit", "of", "--", "a", "bit", "of", "not", "dealing", "with", "just", "the", "friendly", "fire", "all", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "He would be a better guest I guess than I would.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "would", "be", "a", "better", "guest", "I", "guess", "than", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "How's it been for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "it", "been", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I don't think we'll ever get over it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "'ll", "ever", "get", "over", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "What are you thinking when this is all unfurling?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "thinking", "when", "this", "is", "all", "unfurling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I was thinking that it was a nightmare and that I was going to wake up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "thinking", "that", "it", "was", "a", "nightmare", "and", "that", "I", "was", "going", "to", "wake", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "I mean, you I know, John, when you first discovered your daughter was dead, was told did they get the person that did this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "I", "know", ",", "John", ",", "when", "you", "first", "discovered", "your", "daughter", "was", "dead", ",", "was", "told", "did", "they", "get", "the", "person", "that", "did", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "And did it give you any kind of comfort that they had?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "it", "give", "you", "any", "kind", "of", "comfort", "that", "they", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "It definitely did.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "definitely", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Was it cathartic in any sense?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "cathartic", "in", "any", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "It was very difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "very", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Is it hard to reconcile your faith when something like this happens?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "hard", "to", "reconcile", "your", "faith", "when", "something", "like", "this", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "No, not for me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "What are your -- what are your views of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "--", "what", "are", "your", "views", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Well, we do feel, you know, he was mentally disturbed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "do", "feel", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "was", "mentally", "disturbed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "And if people want to help, what do they do?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "people", "want", "to", "help", ",", "what", "do", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Go to ChristinaTaylorGreen.org, and we have a website.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "to", "ChristinaTaylorGreen.org", ",", "and", "we", "have", "a", "website", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]